Volodymyr Lysiuk

Email: volodymyr.lysiuk@gmail.com

Phone: +38 097 941 91 22

Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/in/vlysiuk



Career objective

Desired

At the moment I am interesting in the team leading position and people management area. I like to inspire and motivate people to work together, to achieve the common goals, to be successful as a team and as individuals. I enjoy leading projects and shipping the high-quality products to the customers.

Summary

Certified Agile practitioner and software developer with 10+ years of professional experience. Have a good understanding of software development lifecycle, Agile process and practices that includes managing product backlog, release planning and delivering products to production. My responsibilities include hiring people, managing team progress and relationships among team members, communication with stakeholders. I have experience in building scalable and hi-load applications, have a strong knowledge of design principles and object oriented programming.

Professional experience

December 2019 - Present

Position: Delivery Unit Team Lead at Playtika

Description: My main responsibilities include projects delivery from planning to deploying to production, leading and mentoring cross-functional development team, building the proper development process and product quality, communication with stakeholders

July 2019 – December 2019

Position: Development Team Lead at Global Logic

Description: Working for German company Zeiss. My main responsibility is to scale existing team and build the proper development process for better team performance and predictability for business. I am responsible for building communication between distributed teams and aligning the understanding of the project scope and client priorities

November 2016 – July 2019

Position: Scrum Master/Team Lead

Description: Working for Swedish company Betsson. My responsibility is to grow motivated and high-performed professionals and support them on getting to the established goals. I am also responsible for projects delivery, technical excellence, communication with product owners and architect

November 2014 – July 2019

Position: Senior software developer at Ciklum

Description: Working for Swedish company Betsson. Developing payment system for Betsson Group services. Implementing and maintaining applications and services that require high availability and performance, working on distributed and multi-tier systems

Technical stack: .NET, C#, .NET Core, WCF, MS SQL, Javascript, NServiceBus, Rabbit MQ, Kafka, ASP.NET MVC, LINQ, EntityFramework, NUnit, Specflow, TeamCity, Jira, Git, Docker, Kubernetes

September 2010 – November 2014

Position: Senior software developer at Ciklum

Description: Working for Swedish company Tobii (http://www.tobii.com/)
Developing software for analyzing and processing eye tracking and gaze interaction data. Designing and implementing products for disabled people to help them to communicate with others

Technical stack: .NET, C#, WPF, LINQ, XML, C++, COM, SQLite, EntityFramework, NUnit, Specflow, Moq, TeamCity, Jenkins, Jira, Git, Perforce

April 2008 - September 2010

Position: Senior software developer at Tikle (http://www.tikle.com/)

Description: Developing value-added services and content management systems for one of the biggest Ukrainian mobile operator Life. Designing and implementing operator core services related to subscriptions, campaigns and users data. Holding technical meetings with partners

Technical stack: .NET, C#, ASP.NET, WinForms, MS SQL, ADO.NET, XML, CSS, HTML, SOAP, USSD, SMPP, WAP, SVN

September 2006 - April 2008

Position: Software developer at Tikle

Description: Developing value-added services and content management systems

for one of the biggest Ukrainian mobile operator Life

Technical stack: .NET, C#, ASP.NET, WinForms, MS SQL, ADO.NET, XML, CSS,

HTML, SOAP, USSD, SMPP, WAP, SVN

April 2006 - September 2006

Position: C++ developer at Kvant

Description: Developing modules for a spatial monitoring system. Implementing

algorithms for objects definition and correlation

Technical stack: C++, MFC

September 2004 - April 2006

Position: System administrator, Laboratory assistant at NTUU «KPI» Department

of applied mathematic

Description: Installing and configuring software and hardware. Managing and supporting the local network. Managing users rights and access within the local

domain

Education

2003-2009 NTUU "Kiev Polytechnical Institute"

Department of applied mathematics Faculty of specialized computer system

Master degree

Training Programs

April 2017 - May 2017

Name: Target Course for middle management

Description: How to manage and lead teams, motivation, customer collaboration

Provider: Vera Shatskaya

July 2017

Name: Time management

Description: Time management best practices

Provider: Vera Shatskaya

October 2018 - December 2018

Name: Target course for Business Leaders

Description: Introduction to finance, marketing, project management, customer

collaboration, team leading, risk management

Provider: Ciklum PM Education, Lviv Business School

January 2019 – February 2019

Name: Effective communication

Description: Cultural differences, empathy, active listening, influencing,

negotiations

Provider: Nataliya Ostashko

March 2019

Name: Sales for IT

Description: Leads generation, marketing, customer engagement

Provider: Lviv Business School

Languages

Ukrainian, Russian – native English – fluent

Certificates

Certified scrum master PMI Agile Certified Practitioner